<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Book book_types = "cartoons">
    <Books_details>
        <book_number>Book1</book_number>
            <name>Scrooge Mc Duck</name>
            <Author>Carl Barks</Author>
            <Publisher>Warner Brothers</Publisher>
            <Synopsis>A story about the world's richest duck and his three naughty but cute nephews.</Synopsis>
            <Date_of_Publication>28 September 2021</Date_of_Publication>
            <Language>English</Language>
            <ISBN_number>123456789</ISBN_number>
            <Book_ID>987654321</Book_ID>
            <Famous_quotes>
                "Launchpad, is this a stunt you learned in flight school?"
                "You're a sweet kid, but don't press your luck."
                "You go ahead, Webby dear."
            </Famous_quotes>
        <book_number>Book2</book_number>
            <name>Unicorn - The Mythical Creature</name>
            <Author>Peter S. Beagle</Author>
            <Publisher>Usborne Publishing Ltd</Publisher>
            <Synopsis>The unicorn is a legendary creature that has been described since antiquity as
                a beast with a single large, pointed, spiraling horn projecting from its forehead.
                In European literature and art, the unicorn has for the last thousand years or so
            depicted as a white horse-like or goat-like animal with a long straight horn with
            grooves, cloven hooves, and sometimes a goat's beard. In the Middle Ages and
            Renaissance,it was commonly described as an extremely wild woodland creature,
            a symbol of purity and grace, which could be captured only by a virgin.
            In the encyclopedias, its horn was said to have the power to render poisoned water potable
            and to heal sickness. In medieval and Renaissance times, the tusk of the narwhal was
            sometimes sold as a unicorn horn.</Synopsis>
            <Date_of_Publication>30 June 2006</Date_of_Publication>
            <Language>English</Language>
            <ISBN_number>0746071612</ISBN_number>
            <Book_ID>978-0746071618</Book_ID>
            <Famous_quotes>
                “Life's not easy for unicorns.”
                “The unicorn is not known for its horn, beauty, or purity; but for its strength and courage as one.”
                “You may have stopped believing in unicorns, but they never stopped believing in you.”
            </Famous_quotes>
        <book_number>Book3</book_number>
            <name>Chip and Dale</name>
            <Author>Dick Kinney</Author>
            <Publisher>Disney Comics</Publisher>
            <Synopsis>Chip and Dale (also spelled Chip 'n' Dale or Chip an' Dale) are duo of cartoon characters<br>
            created in 1943 by The Walt Disney Company.
            As anthropomorphic chipmunk brothers,[2] their names are a pun on the name of the
            18th-century cabinet maker and furniture designer Thomas Chippendale.
            This was suggested by Bill "Tex" Henson, a story artist at the studio.
            The characters were first introduced in the 1943 Pluto short Private Pluto,
            directed by Clyde Geronimi, in which they fight with Pluto about whether they
            can store their nuts in a military base cannon.</Synopsis>
            <Date_of_Publication>June 1990 – December 1991</Date_of_Publication>
            <Language>English</Language>
            <ISBN_number>0746071612</ISBN_number>
            <Book_ID>34546576</Book_ID>
            <Famous_quotes>
                "That was a close one.Are you OK Dale?"
                "Yeah. Luckily it landed on my head."
                "We can't waste our time playing pirates. We're Rescue Rangers. We've got jobs to do."
            </Famous_quotes>
    </Books_details>
</Book>